{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who should post on organization website?",
      "correct_answer": "Only Authorized Persons",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Anyone",
        "IT Team",
        "No one"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What will happen if user reveal company's secret on social media?",
      "correct_answer": "Discipilonary Action",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Nothing",
        "Warning",
        "Appreciation"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "How many colors are there in a rainbow?",
      "correct_answer": "7",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "8",
        "9",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Should you insert devices that can harm the network or can lead to data breach?",
      "correct_answer": "Never",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Can Try",
        "Sometime",
        "Yes"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Use Encryption software for confidential data?",
      "correct_answer": "Always",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "May Be",
        "Don't Know",
        "Never"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Should you modify the data that you don't have access?",
      "correct_answer": "Never",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Can Try",
        "Maybe",
        "Don't Know"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the name of NASA&rsquo;s most famous space telescope?",
      "correct_answer": "Hubble Space Telescope",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Big Eye",
        "Death Star",
        "Millenium Falcon"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What are Panama hats made out of?",
      "correct_answer": "Straw",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Silk",
        "Hemp",
        "Flax"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The Canadian $1 coin is colloquially known as a what?",
      "correct_answer": "Loonie",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Boolie",
        "Foolie",
        "Moodie"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the famous Papa John&#039;s last name?",
      "correct_answer": "Schnatter",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Chowder",
        "Williams",
        "ANDERSON"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
